Institution:
    Tennessee Orthopaedic Clinics
    MRI

Media Creator Application:
    Name of the product: MRI Scan System

Vendor Information:
    Esaote S.p.A.
    Web site: www.esaote.com

Media Viewer Application:
    - Operating systems supported: Windows XP, Windows 2000, Windows VISTA, Windows 7

    - Name of the product: Esaote Viewer Lite    MRI EVOlution 21 Release 9.02.00 F090101 E-MRI Brio BUILD_176 3/12/2021 

    - Disclaimer statement:
        The intended use of the Esaote Viewer Lite is to display the MRI Dicom studies stored within the media.
        The software provided is not a reporting tool, is not for diagnostic imaging.
        as to its use or performance

    - List of minimum requirements:
        Microsoft Service Pack 4 for Windows 2000
        Internet Explorer 6.0 SPI (minimum)
        Adobe Acrobat Reader 5.0 or later version
        Graphics card with 16MB VRAM
        256 MB RAM
        CD-rom/DVD drive and/or optical-magnetic disk drive.
        Color monitor, minimum requirements: 17', resolution 1280 × 1024,
        24 bit, VGA = 60 Hz

Overall Media Organization:
    DICOM composite objects are located in the folder DICOM.
    The Media Viewer Application is located in the folder VIEWER.
    PDI Web Option data is located in the folder IHE_PDI.

Compliance options:
    This device conforms to the IHE Portable Data for Imaging (PDI) Integration Profile.

    - for CD-R only
        This device also conforms to the DICOM General Purpose CD-R Interchange Profile.

    - for DVD only
        This device also conforms to the DICOM General Purpose DVD Interchange with JPEG Profile.

    - for USB only
        This device also conforms to the DICOM General Purpose USB Media Interchange with JPEG Profile.
